[{"answer": "That's what's said happened and that's what's going around, that the kids made or were attempting to make a run or to escape.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "But did it surprise you that in that moment, even at his young age, that he was showing such enterprising courage?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "My feelings towards the shooter is, it was a cowardly thing he did.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 64, "question": "What are your feelings towards the shooter himself?", "qSentId": 63}, {"answer": "You know, there is no single, simple solution.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "What is the most constructive, definitive thing that America's lawmakers can now do?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "I really am sensing that there is an openness and willingness on the part of a lot of people who never would have considered before to actually consider, for example, a ban on assault weapons which, as everybody knows, were designed for military use and right now even in the states that have them, like my state of Connecticut, and I know because I helped write the bill and then I personally defended it in court, in the trial, in the argument before state Supreme Court when it was challenged constitutionally.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "Are you really sensing, from your colleagues, that this is a tipping point?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "There's been an outpouring all across America of people wanting to help and to give.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 157, "question": "Have you noticed this?", "qSentId": 156}, {"answer": "I am hopeful.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 173, "question": "Are you optimistic that there will be one before we all tumble over this cliff?", "qSentId": 172}, {"answer": "Yes, sir, I do.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "Mr. Keller, you agree with Rick Perry?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "ELLER: No, not at all.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "And your idea is that all teachers would be armed?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "That's correct, whether it be the weapons or the concealed carry class that I teach, either one.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 204, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 203}, {"answer": "I've thought about that a lot in the last couple of days.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Where would these teachers who are armed put the guns when they are in school?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "When we can get them.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Do you sell AR-15 rifles?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "ELLER: I'm just -- I'm against any banning of any weapons that we are today.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "I'm aware of that.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Are you aware of that?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "No, that's not the solution, sir.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "That would be your solution?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "My comment was that the person who is defending his place, whether it be a school or a theater, if they are trained properly, they can shoot one time and they take out the person who is spraying bullets.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "You are aware that these weapons did unleash many, many, many bullets, are you, and killed many, many people?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "Yes, it certainly did.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "This must have brought back particularly painful memories to you?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "No, it wasn't.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 308, "question": "But it wasn't political in anyway like the same way back in Britain, was it?", "qSentId": 307}, {"answer": "Well, the level of gun crime in Britain is very low compared with the U.S. Gun crime has been falling in England every year for the last eight years.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 311, "question": "What impact did the ban on handguns have in Britain?", "qSentId": 310}, {"answer": "I just do not understand the logic of that.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "I think one of the main strengths that those of us who lost children in Dunblane found was being brought together.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 327, "question": "Is there any advice that you can give them, any words of comfort from somebody who's, quite literally, lived through what they've gone through?", "qSentId": 326}, {"answer": "Well, I think when a thing like this happens, obviously all questions are on the table and deserve an answer, if you can get one.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 359, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 358}, {"answer": "I was very happy.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "\"The Sopranos,\" much missed show, one of my favorites on television, when it came to an end, what were your honest feelings?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "Here's all I remember coherently, was that there's this Elvis Costello song \"Radio, Radio,\" the lyrics of which are \"I want to bite the hand that feeds me.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Did you hope to have one?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "I was lucky.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "I tried very hard.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 406, "question": "Why now, quite late in your career, to plunge into the big screen?", "qSentId": 405}, {"answer": "I didn't -- I wasn't thinking about Jim originally for this, for the role of the father.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Why did you want him?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "I wanted to be a rock 'n' roll musician.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 432, "question": "They're suggesting it's kind of autobiographical for you, that when you were young, you wanted to be a rock star?", "qSentId": 431}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Didn't see yourself on stage, long hair, big guitar, strutting your stuff?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "I -- I am happy.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Are you ever happy with your work?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 462, "question": "You were?", "qSentId": 461}, {"answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "docId": "121220pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Is that a compliment?", "qSentId": 466}]